Peter C. Bunnell Papers, circa 1857-2018 (bulk 1960-2018): Finding Aid C1629
Manuscripts Division
- Writings, 1960-2017; 10 boxes
  - Publications, 1960-2017; 8 boxes (Box B-001328, Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 101, Box 102, Box 103)
    This file group includes publications by or contributed to by Bunnell, such as his dissertations, magazine and journal articles, photography books, and his own works as main author or editor. Many of the publications that Bunnell wrote a biography for, reviewed, or contributed to are inscribed to him by the primary authors or photographers of the work. Notable signers include Ruth Bernhard, Michael Kenna, Jerry Uelsmann, Barbara Morgan, and Max Waldman. Also included is the run of show for Bunnell's appearance on National Educational Television's (NET) Time, Light, and Vision: The Art of Photography program in February 1967.
  - Drafts, 1966-2006; 2 boxes
    This file group includes drafts and proofs of articles and books that Bunnell wrote, edited, or contributed to. Two anthologies that he edited, A Photographic Vision: Pictorial Photography, 1889-1923 (1980) and Aperture Magazine Anthology: The Minor White Years, 1952–1976 (2012), are included here, as well as text for two exhibition catalogues for Nina Alexander and Clarence H. White ( Clarence H. White: The Reverence for Beauty, 1986).
    - Princeton University Press Proposal, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Peter C. Bunnell Anthology of Own Writings, 1969-1984; 6 folders (Box 104, Folder 2-7)
    - Aperture Anthology, 2006; 6 folders (Box 104, Folder 8-13)
    - Pictorialism Article/Chapter, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 105, Folder 1-2)
    - The City: American Experience, circa 1971; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Nina Alexander Catalogue, 1987; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Clarence H. White - Ohio University Catalogue, circa 1966; 3 folders (Box 105, Folder 5-7)
    - A Photographic Vision: Pictorial Photography, 1889-1923, circa 1980; 9 folders (Box 105, Folder 8-16)
- Photographs, 2002; 1 box
  This file group includes photographs of Bunnell's retirement from Princeton University in 2002.
  - Retirement Dinner Snaps, 2002; 1 box (Box 60)